[{"answer": "With a little bit of caution, they don't really know the numbers yet, OK.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What was the explanation for that?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "You know, when we were in Haiti, Piers, in January of 2010, rescues were happening days and weeks later so we can always hope for that.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Is it possible that there are still people that are trapped?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "That is correct.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Everybody at the funeral saw them leave and it was believed they were heading back to Moore?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, the Moore Police Department and the Highway Patrol both, we wanted to put out a silver alert on them since they are both very elderly and in bad health, and we were told they're not doing that at this time because of the catastrophe, and all we can do is file missing persons reports with the Red Cross and put them on registration lists here and there.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What are the authorities telling you when you've asked them about this?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": ", DROVE 100 MILES TO FIND SON: Well, I'm an educator in the Putnam City School District and I had to stay at my school to make sure our students were safe, and I was watching the TV as the tornado was heading down towards Gabriel's school, and as soon as it hit the school, I was able to just rush home and just go 100 miles an hour on the highway and went through neighborhoods and had to run about a mile, and hop -- got some -- got on a couple of trucks and took about three and a half hours to find him.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "And what did you do?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes, I can.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Julie Simon, can you hear me?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "It was like the three little pigs.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What was the experience like in terms of the power and the damage that it was causing?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I want to say she's a really nice teacher, and she was the best teacher I ever had.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Gabriel, what do you want to say to your teacher?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I don't know if we can say anything.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What would you say to her?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "She's fine.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Is she okay?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like this in your life?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Everything I've heard, they're very close as far as miles per hour, but you're talking about one of them being 225 and one being 210 or something.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Is it worse?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "I mean are we in a situation now where you believe everybody is accounted for?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "It could be.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Is it possible that they could still be somewhere just not found, trapped or whatever?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Would you be prepared to take a look at it for them, because they seem pretty desperate for some kind of information?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "They have been trained to do this before?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Yes, they were under the desks.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Were they in the same room as you?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Did you keep it?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, we actually stayed in the hospital, but we had -- I think the hospital did a great job of giving us some warnings.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "How much warning did you get to get out of there?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "It was -- I've lived here in Oklahoma all my life, and I've seen them, I've been around them.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What was it like to actually experience the full blast of this tornado?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "When you woke up today and saw the scale of what had gone on, do you feel as I do that it's bordering on miraculous that the death toll at the moment is at 24 and not much, much higher?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, of course, an adrenaline rush with the situation that was happening.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What was going through your mind as you raced to the scene and then realized what have happened?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Yes, exactly.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "But, from a human perspective, you must have been thinking what on earth has happened to this area that I know so well?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "It's really difficult to tell from myself, having seen them both from the air and from the ground.", "docId": "130521pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "I know one of the local papers, it may have been yours that said that, but do you believe that to be the case?", "qSentId": 584}]